{
  "name": "",
  "isFavorite": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Doctor",
      "back": "Doktor"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Nurse",
      "back": "Hemşire"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Teacher",
      "back": "Öğretmen"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Student",
      "back": "Öğrenci"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Police officer",
      "back": "Polis memuru"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Firefighter",
      "back": "İtfaiyeci"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Engineer",
      "back": "Mühendis"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Mechanic",
      "back": "Tamirci"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Chef",
      "back": "Aşçı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Waiter",
      "back": "Garson"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Farmer",
      "back": "Çiftçi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pilot",
      "back": "Pilot"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Driver",
      "back": "Şoför"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Dentist",
      "back": "Diş hekimi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Lawyer",
      "back": "Avukat"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Judge",
      "back": "Hakim"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Scientist",
      "back": "Bilim insanı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Artist",
      "back": "Sanatçı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Singer",
      "back": "Şarkıcı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Actor",
      "back": "Oyuncu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cleaner",
      "back": "Temizlikçi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Builder",
      "back": "İnşaatçı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Plumber",
      "back": "Tesisatçı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Electrician",
      "back": "Elektrikçi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tailor",
      "back": "Terzi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Hairdresser",
      "back": "Kuaför"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Postman",
      "back": "Postacı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Soldier",
      "back": "Asker"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Translator",
      "back": "Çevirmen"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Photographer",
      "back": "Fotoğrafçı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Journalist",
      "back": "Gazeteci"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Carpenter",
      "back": "Marangoz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Librarian",
      "back": "Kütüphaneci"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Architect",
      "back": "Mimar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Musician",
      "back": "Müzisyen"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Veterinarian",
      "back": "Veteriner"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Flight attendant",
      "back": "Hostes"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Receptionist",
      "back": "Resepsiyonist"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Programmer",
      "back": "Yazılımcı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "IT specialist",
      "back": "Bilgi işlem uzmanı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Banker",
      "back": "Bankacı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cashier",
      "back": "Kasiyer"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Shop assistant",
      "back": "Satış danışmanı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Manager",
      "back": "Müdür"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "CEO",
      "back": "Genel Müdür"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Security guard",
      "back": "Güvenlik görevlisi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Janitor",
      "back": "Hizmetli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Model",
      "back": "Model"
    }
  ]
}
